I remember a year ago in February 2020
when the story started coming out about
Kyle cease and how much anger and
disconnect there was in the community
for for a few weeks and then the
community had this huge shift where they
were able to see that Kyle had been
telling the truth all along he wasn't
supposed to be our coach he wasn't
supposed to be our guru he was supposed
to be one among many of the world
changers and so we took the learning we
had gotten and created our own community
evolving out loud without Kyle sees
all-access pass to each other we created
weekly calls that we could show up on
and without it being centered on one
central leader we were able to to
discuss the insights we all had and
create mastermind type groups to be the
world changers that that we we knew
that's what called us to this work
that's what called us here and the
things that have come out of it in the
last year of us all stepping into our
power together of us all creating what
was effectively a decentralized coaching
method where anyone can show up and get
the presence and authenticity they need
to move forward where there wasn't this
hierarchical dynamic of the coach and
the coaching or whatever that word was
which we don't even need anymore that we
were able to see our own power and I
just I can't wait to see what 2021 holds
for the rest of the year because all the
things that came to light in 2020 like
teal salon had said have although they
were hard they were hard to hear at the
time they were hard they were like
soul-crushing heartbreaking for many of
us at the time now I can see that that
was all just the the symptoms of a
disease it was
all just like you know the runny nose
and temperature that you have when you
have a cold it's like fighting that that
infection off it was us wanting that
leader that we could we could look up to
and would give us the answers and
instead we all stepped into our power
simultaneously an entire community of
thousands of people who were looking up
to him and even in a small way actually
just let him go and created our own
community around each other and instead
of it being 30 bucks a month we put 10
bucks a month into a pool and we use
that to to pay for the the tools and
infrastructure that we needed in order
to be able to come together and create
those those group coaching calls and to
show up for one another and still follow
the things that resonated with us we
were still able to to Diego as we now
call it and we were able to love that
truly love that in a way that we could
see nobody's ever gonna be perfect no
one's ever gonna be that guru or that
leader we don't need to be that we are
free from that we're freed from ever
that is not what it needed to look like
it needed to look like our actual
authenticity showing up that when you
need to be getting money from it you're
automatically not going to be stepping
into your authenticity if you're if
you're in any way going for the money
over the authenticity and so we let the
money go we let those that could put 10
bucks into the pool and those that
couldn't didn't put 10 bucks Tan and now
a year later nearly everyone is putting
$10 in because that was part of what we
we discussed it's like what would get
this worth it for you and now we're able
to have this resiliency this this
financial and emotional and structural
resiliency because it's not designed
around one leader it's designed around
all of us be leaders and if something
comes to light as it constantly does on
these calls it's not soul-crushing and
heart-wrenching because it's not the
fall from grace of a central leader and
then you're scared this whole community
is gonna collapse it's how can we
support you how can we support you and
your
how can we help you no matter who it is
and and a year later just a couple weeks
ago Kyle came and he's one among many he
has seen the error of his way to seeing
the pain that he caused and and this is
part of his vision although it hurt him
a year ago when we all left and he
didn't have that money anymore now he
can see that this was part of what he
was doing and everything did unfold
exactly as it was supposed to and thank
goodness those women came forward and
told us the truth it was hard to hear
and it was hard for the people who
looked up to him and and it saw them as
the reason it was falling apart and
through their anger and frustration
towards them and others did it towards
Kyle but we're all human and we're all
in it together and now a year later what
an amazing community we have that is is
interwoven and everyone can show up and
just be can be authentic and gee do I
love that